So we've met a new MEP guy today. We've
shown him the place for our...
Aditya.
Yeah, Aditya. We've shown
him the place for our train.
Still can be an issue. They just don't
want to give us the space for the water,
for the drinking water.
They just want us to use the bottles. But
we'll try to, you know, battle them.
Also, finally, I guess and I hope that
Manchini will cover the
part of the design thing.
Because I have nobody
left. Everybody is busy.
Which design?
Design for the studio. The
wall, the back wall design.
So they take into
consideration what kind of a screen.
Isn't that mostly treatment?
Yeah, it's mostly treatment. But anyway,
it should look good.
We covered in the meeting very important
things. The biggest one was the FCU.
The noise level should be controlled,
thoroughly controlled.
It was the biggest pain
point, highest priority point.
We lost one FCU on the
drawings. Now it's bad.
Yeah, so they had a wrong thing. It was
incomplete. They were short on that.
That was the biggest
point that's covered.
A variant.
We went through the samples he gave us to
decide on the material
design, whatever it's going to be.
And the shape is obviously dependent on
the curve of the wall. It is what it is.
They will squeeze as much desk that's
possible in that space.
I told them to get brushed metal legs by
the way. They look nice.
Brushed metal, like this, kind of. Grey,
brushed metal. Looks very nice.
We have black. They said no problem.
That's not an issue.
And the other thing is that we told them
carpet wise, super
thick carpet in the studio.
And then maybe less thick
in the general office area.
And of course, we are having some kind of
a soft argument about
green on green, green on.
I want bright, vivid colors. I don't want
the place to look like a regular office
with dull, subdued colors.
It needs to pop. Business doesn't need to
be dull. Business can be health,
vibrancy, natural
colors, green, all of that.
Shouldn't be boring.
Shouldn't be boring. We are not boring.
We're going to make business fun and
entertaining and useful.
It's day to day, you know, like business
is fun. Business is
life. Everything is business.
And then another thing, they're going to
try to put in another rack by the way.
I told them that can you
squeeze in like a split rack.
Is it going to be the 47?
No, no, there's not enough space. So they
are going to look for a low profile rack
to squeeze somehow as a man.
Let's not waste. They said we put it on
our wheels because the last time he
showed me all of that stuff, it was
looking pretty full.
And then having like a like they will
move the non-movable stuff
in that rack split the gear.
So for because otherwise we will be like
you remember we have an
idea to have something.
We need the desk. Yes.
Of the equipment, right. Not generate
that much of a sound.
So we told what we told broadcast
solutions that make the desk a storage
desk basically like, you know, we're not
using it like like an extra storage space
because it's a very big desk.
Dense desk effectively and can be just
why not just put compartments everywhere,
boxes everywhere you can have it.
It's going to be off air anyway. It's not
going to be on camera shots. That's that.
Why you choose the
broadcast solution? Why?
Oh, that was a long process.
Out of all the companies that connected
the four ideas, these ones were more
professional in just their response.
We went through a very rigorous process
of a couple of months of getting the
solution, talking to them and then why
broadcast solutions?
Very important point because they are the
glue basically, they're the builders.
It's not about OK, even I could have gone
to the market and buy all this stuff and
then start building it.
But they have the team around the right
people who will not make
the mistakes on the wiring.
They will. I told them that this is a
this is a partnership.
It's not just that, oh, I am the client.
I demand this to happen. That's not how
it works in technology.
It needs to be the right thing, right way
to do it, not my way to do it.
It should be the correct way. So we went
through a couple of players.
One of the players just disappeared and
the second player was
like, no, wishy washy.
We were like trying to.
He's always agreeing on everything that
we ask and no technical
specification under it.
So nothing really seemed
to be real at this point.
So every every conversation will end up.
Yeah, we can do that. But can you really?
So broadcast solutions were the guys who
literally sat with us
and explained step by step.
How is it going to work? What do we need
for it? And can it be made or not?
Can it happen? And the main thing with
broadcast solutions from day one, they
responded to our email on time.
And every meeting, every response was on
time, never delayed.
Everything was on the dot. And it was
even then, even when we had the win
media, which is our
main automation solution,
they didn't understand how to do the
presentation with our account manager,
product account owner, Lauren.
He explained to them that I was just
asking them to do a day in the life of a
station, not a training video.
Everyone was trying to do a training
video. So let's do a train like a day in
the life of a station.
Being like a professional here, according
to my little experience here in Dubai is
a pretty rare thing.
So usually it's just like, yeah, yeah,
this and that. They forgot like in a
month, they responded.
And just again, the quotation is
different. Everything is different.
Everything is different. Oh, I forgot to
do that. So
everything's like mass, very messy.
But with broadcast solutions, it was
pretty like everything
was clear from the start.
Yeah, no double talk,
nothing always on time.
It was the deliverable. Even the way even
then we didn't have we
didn't pay them any money.
They're the quality of responses was OK,
I'm going to be late.
Even if it's few minutes, you know, like
you see all of those things, we realize,
OK, in a project, you need that.
OK, we're good.
Here, man. Hope it wasn't too boring.
It's all right.
Just realize that it's not boring to
someone who cares about.